hey guys this looks like a fun one I
think we would call it a radical
equation first step to solve this I want
to get rid of this radical right here so
let's copy this down and square both
sides on the right hand side this square
and square root are going to cancel each
other out giving us just the inside
stuff and we could just copy down the
left hand side normally with these we
would multiply this out but this has a
matching one right here so we're just
going to subtract that from both sides
the left hand side is just going to be 0
and the right hand side we bring down
this other stuff and smush them together
let's bring this to the other side and
add 8 to both sides these cancel so the
left hand side is just this and the
right hand side is going to be eight now
to get rid of this square root we're
going to square both sides again the
left hand side is just going to be this
Inside Stuff x minus 4 and the right
side is going to be 64. add 4 to both
sides and we get x equals 68 how
exciting